Simon Fraser University Library fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Committee records, 1966 - 1997; F-50-9; 1.98 m of textual records 173 photographs: prints; black and white; Physical description: 173 photographs located in F-50-9-8-0-9
  - Staff Committee, 1968 - 1975; F-50-9-8; 15 cm of textual records 173 photographs: prints; black and white
    - Correspondence and minutes, vol. 2, 1968 - 1972; F-50-9-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-95)
  - Building Committee, 1972 - 1974; F-50-9-9; 3 cm of textual records
    - Building Committee - Terms of Reference, 1973; F-50-9-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - Building Committee, 1972 - 1974; F-50-9-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - Building Committee - Memoranda, 1972 - 1974; F-50-9-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
  - Planning and Budgeting Committee, 1974 - 1975; F-50-9-10; 1 cm of textual records
    - Planning and Budgeting Meetings, 1974 - 1975; F-50-9-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
  - Bibliographic Control Advisory Committee (BCAC), 1976 - 1979; F-50-9-12; 4 cm of textual records
    - BCAC - Terms of Reference, 1976 - 1979; F-50-9-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - BCAC - Memoranda and Minutes, 1976 - 1979; F-50-9-12-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1976 - 1979; F-50-9-12-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-96)
  - Public Services Committee, 1971 - 1978; F-50-9-13; 5 cm of textual records
    - Public Services committee - Terms of Reference, 1976 - 1978; F-50-9-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - Public Services committee, 1976 - 1978; F-50-9-13-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - Exhibition Committee minutes, 1971; F-50-9-13-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - Correspondence and policies, 1976 - 1978; F-50-9-13-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-96)
      Creator's original file classification code: II-A-14.
  - Library Management Committee, 1978 - 1992; F-50-9-14; 31 cm of textual records
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1978; F-50-9-14-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1978; F-50-9-14-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1979; F-50-9-14-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1979; F-50-9-14-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1980; F-50-9-14-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1980; F-50-9-14-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1981; F-50-9-14-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1981; F-50-9-14-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1982; F-50-9-14-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1983; F-50-9-14-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1984 - 1988; F-50-9-14-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda, Minutes, and Papers, 1989 - 1990; F-50-9-14-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1992; F-50-9-14-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-62)
    - Minutes, 1979; F-50-9-14-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-96)
      Creator's original file classification code: II-A-5.
    - Minutes, 1980; F-50-9-14-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-96)
    - Minutes, vol. 1, 1981; F-50-9-14-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-96)
    - Minutes, vol. 2, 1981; F-50-9-14-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-97)
    - Minutes, 1982; F-50-9-14-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-97)
    - Minutes, 1983; F-50-9-14-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-97)
    - Minutes, 1984; F-50-9-14-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-97)
    - Minutes, 1985; F-50-9-14-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-97)
    - Minutes, 1986; F-50-9-14-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-97)
    - Correspondence and budget planning, vol. 1, 1985 - 1988; F-50-9-14-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-97)
    - Correspondence and budget planning, vol. 2, 1985 - 1988; F-50-9-14-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-97)
  - Library Executive Committee, 1969 - 1975; F-50-9-15; 5 cm of textual records
    - Minutes (bound), 1969 - 1971; F-50-9-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-98)
    - Minutes (bound), 1971 - 1972; F-50-9-15-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-98)
    - Minutes (bound), 1973 - 1975; F-50-9-15-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-98)
  - Committee of Heads, 1967 - 1976; F-50-9-11; 8 cm of textual records
    - Committee of Heads - Terms of Reference, 1973; F-50-9-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - Committee of Heads, 1973 - 1975; F-50-9-11-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-61)
    - Committee of Heads - Papers CH1-CH11, 1973 - 1974; F-50-9-11-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-59)
    - Minutes (bound), 1967 - 1975; F-50-9-11-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-96)
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1973 - 1975; F-50-9-11-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-96)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/72.
    - Correspondence, 1975 - 1976; F-50-9-11-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-96)
      Creator's original file classification code: II-A-3.
  - Library Systems Group, 1987 - 1989; F-50-9-16; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1987 - 1989; F-50-9-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-98)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/54d.
  - Association of SFU Librarians, 1972 - 1974; F-50-9-17; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1972 - 1974; F-50-9-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-98)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/38.
  - Publications Committee, 1984; F-50-9-18; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1984; F-50-9-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-98)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/141.
  - Electronic Resources Committee, 1995 - 1996; F-50-9-19; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1995 - 1996; F-50-9-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-98)
  - Media Collections Committee, 1972 - 1973; F-50-9-20; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1972 - 1973; F-50-9-20-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-98)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/26.
  - BCIT - Library Advisory Committee, 1970 - 1975; F-50-9-21; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1970 - 1975; F-50-9-21-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/50.
  - Deputy Librarian Staff Group, 1976 - 1977; F-50-9-22; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1976 - 1977; F-50-9-22-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/77.
  - Library Administration Task Force, 1980; F-50-9-23; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1980; F-50-9-23-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
      Creator's original file classification code: 7000/4.
  - University Archives Committee, 1984; F-50-9-24; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1984; F-50-9-24-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/139.
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Status, 1968 - 1974; F-50-9-25; 1 cm of textual records
    Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Status
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1968 - 1974; F-50-9-25-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/134.
  - Computerized Information Retrieval Services Committee, 1979 - 1981; F-50-9-26; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1979 - 1981; F-50-9-26-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
  - Steering Committee for Library's Strategic Plan Implementation, 1991 - 1994; F-50-9-27; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1991 - 1994; F-50-9-27-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
  - Interprovincial Committee on University Rationalization, 1968 - 1972; F-50-9-28; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1968 - 1972; F-50-9-28-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/117.
  - External Library Review Committee, 1973 - 1975; F-50-9-29; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1973 - 1975; F-50-9-29-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-99)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/20.
  - Senate Library Committee, 1978 - 1987; F-50-9-30; 6 cm of textual records
    Senate Library Committee
    - Minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1978 - 1987; F-50-9-30-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-100)
    - Minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1978 - 1987; F-50-9-30-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-100)
    - Correspondence, 1979 - 1983; F-50-9-30-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-100)
  - Library Space Committee, 1983 - 1986; F-50-9-31; 4 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1983 - 1986; F-50-9-31-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-100)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1983 - 1986; F-50-9-31-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-100)
  - Library Safety Committee, 1992 - 1997; F-50-9-32; 6 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1992 - 1997; F-50-9-32-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-100)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1992 - 1997; F-50-9-32-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-101)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 3, 1992 - 1997; F-50-9-32-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-101)
  - SFU Staff Association, 1966 - 1975; F-50-9-33; 6 cm of textual records
    Simon Fraser University Staff Association
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1966 - 1975; F-50-9-33-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-101)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/80.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1966 - 1975; F-50-9-33-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-101)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1966 - 1975; F-50-9-33-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-101)
  - SFU Librarian's Committee, 1969 - 1971; F-50-9-34; 2 cm of textual records
    - Minutes, 1969 - 1971; F-50-9-34-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-101)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/2.
  - Library Review Committee, 1984 - 1993; F-50-9-35; 25 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1984; F-50-9-35-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-102)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/136.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1984; F-50-9-35-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-102)
    - Division reports, 1991; F-50-9-35-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-102)
    - Samuel and Frances Belzberg Library report, 1991; F-50-9-35-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-102)
    - GEAC background and reports, 1991; F-50-9-35-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-102)
    - Library user survey, 1991; F-50-9-35-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-102)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1991 - 1992; F-50-9-35-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-102)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/137.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1991 - 1992; F-50-9-35-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-103)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 3, 1991 - 1992; F-50-9-35-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-103)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 4, 1991 - 1992; F-50-9-35-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-103)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 5, 1991 - 1992; F-50-9-35-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-103)
    - Library Review Implementation Committee, 1992 - 1993; F-50-9-35-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-103)
      Creator's original file classification code: 6000/137a.
- Publications, 1965 - 2006; F-50-10; 60 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications produced by the University Library and include lists of serials held by the Library, Library handbooks and annual reports, brochures, newsletters and bulletins, faculty guides, subject bibliographies, publishing guidelines for theses and extended essays and projects, SFU Friends of the Library event publications, and Library survey result reports.
  The publications found in this series were acquired by the Archives from a variety of sources. Although accessions from the University Library contained a number of publications, most of the records were collected by Archives staff as part of an artificial university-wide publications collection and then processed as part of the fonds.
  - Serials lists, 1965 - 1970; F-50-10-1; 13 cm of textual records
    - Printed Serials lists, 1965; F-50-10-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-63)
    - Printed Serials lists, 1965; F-50-10-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-63)
    - Printed Serials lists, 1966; F-50-10-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-63)
    - Printed Serials lists, 1966; F-50-10-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-63)
    - Printed Serials lists, 1967; F-50-10-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-63)
    - Printed Serials lists, 1968; F-50-10-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-63)
    - Printed Serials lists, 1969; F-50-10-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-63)
    - Printed Serials lists, 1970; F-50-10-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-63)
  - General publications, 1965 - 2006; F-50-10-2; 47 cm of textual records
    - Introduction and Guide, 1965 - 1970; F-50-10-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Use of the Library and Regulations, 1965; F-50-10-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Library Handbooks and Bookmarks, 1969 - 1980; F-50-10-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Chit-Chat, 1970 - 1990; F-50-10-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Medium, No.1-2, 1970; F-50-10-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Source, v.1, No.1 - v.2, No.4, 1971 - 1972; F-50-10-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - SFU Library News Monthly, 1974 - 1975; F-50-10-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Information Bulletin, 1967 - 1968; F-50-10-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Information Bulletin, 1968 - 1969; F-50-10-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Information Bulletin, 1969 - 1970; F-50-10-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
      Open
    - Faculty Guides, 1967 - 1969; F-50-10-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-64)
    - Humanities: Bibliographies, No.1-6, 1967 - 1970; F-50-10-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-65)
    - Humanities: Bibliographies, 1970 - 1976; F-50-10-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-65)
    - Sciences: Bibliographies, 1970 - 1971; F-50-10-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-65)
    - Social Sciences: Bibliographies, No.1-18, 1966 - 1971; F-50-10-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-65)
    - Theses, Extended Essays and Projects, 1971; F-50-10-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-65)
    - Theses, Extended Essays and Projects, 1976; F-50-10-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-65)
    - Theses, Extended Essays and Projects, 1978; F-50-10-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-65)
    - Theses, Extended Essays and Projects, 1979; F-50-10-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-65)
    - Monthly Accessions List, 1975; F-50-10-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-66)
    - Outline Databases, 1980; F-50-10-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-66)
    - Policy and Procedure for Computerized Information Retrieval Services (CIRS), 1981; F-50-10-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-66)
    - Library Operations and Support Services Bulletin, 1-42, 1976 - 1977; F-50-10-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-66)
    - Library Newsletter No 1, 1985; F-50-10-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-66)
    - Glissade v. 1, 1985; F-50-10-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-66)
    - Library brochures, 1989 - 2006; F-50-10-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - Innovating newsletter, 1994 - 1995; F-50-10-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - Information Bulletin, 1994 - 1998; F-50-10-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - Special Collections exhibitions, 1995; F-50-10-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - SFU Friends of the Library event publications, 1996 - 1997; F-50-10-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - Results from a survey of SFU students, 1997; F-50-10-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - Results from a survey of SFU faculty, 1997; F-50-10-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - SFU Library Annual Report, 1998 - 1999; F-50-10-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - SFU Library News, 1998 - 2003; F-50-10-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - SFU Library Annual Report, 1999 - 2000; F-50-10-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - SFU Library Annual Report, 2000 - 2001; F-50-10-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
    - Friends of SFU Library newsletter, 2003 - 2004; F-50-10-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
- University Bookstore records, 1970 - 1999; F-50-11; 57 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the University Bookstore and includes correspondence of the University Librarian with the Bookstore manager, the university community regarding the Bookstore, and vendors; Bookstore policies and operating procedures; year end reports; a Bookstore research study; operating budget and financial statements; plans for renovations to the Bookstore; the report of the Bookstore Review Committee and responses to it; and records of a joint grievance committee hearing.
  Records include correspondence, reports, budget and financial working papers, and newsletters.
  - Bookstore policies, 1972 - 1986; F-50-11-0-0-1 (Archival box - small 50-67)
  - A Report on Bookstore, 1970; F-50-11-0-0-2 (Archival box - small 50-67)
  - University Librarians Response to Report on Bookstore, 1970; F-50-11-0-0-3 (Archival box - small 50-67)
  - Newsletter, 1987 - 1989; F-50-11-0-0-4 (Archival box - small 50-67)
  - Correspondence, 1977; F-50-11-0-0-5 (Archival box - small 50-67)
  - Joint Grievance Committee Hearing, 1984; F-50-11-0-0-6 (Archival box - small 50-67)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1971 - 1973; F-50-11-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1971 - 1973; F-50-11-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 3, 1971 - 1973; F-50-11-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-104)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1973 - 1977; F-50-11-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-105)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1973 - 1977; F-50-11-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-105)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1977 - 1980; F-50-11-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-105)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1977 - 1980; F-50-11-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-105)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1981 - 1985; F-50-11-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-105)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1981 - 1985; F-50-11-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-105)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1985 - 1987; F-50-11-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-106)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1985 - 1987; F-50-11-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-106)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1988 - 1991; F-50-11-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-106)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1988 - 1991; F-50-11-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-106)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1991 - 1995; F-50-11-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-106)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1991 - 1995; F-50-11-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-107)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1995 - 1997; F-50-11-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 50-107)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1995 - 1997; F-50-11-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 50-107)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 1, 1997 - 1999; F-50-11-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 50-107)
  - Correspondence, reports and working papers, vol. 2, 1997 - 1999; F-50-11-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 50-107)
  - SFU Bookstore Research Study, 1983; F-50-11-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
  - Year End Report, 1987; F-50-11-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
  - Operating budget, 1987; F-50-11-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
  - Operating budget, 1988; F-50-11-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
  - Bookstore renovation/expansion, 1979 - 1982; F-50-11-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
  - Bookstore Review Committee - working papers, 1970 - 1983; F-50-11-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
  - Bookstore review, 1984; F-50-11-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
  - Bookstore Review Committee - working papers, 1984 - 1985; F-50-11-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
- Tri Universities Libraries (TRIUL) records, 1970 - 1989; F-50-12; 47 cm of textual records; Tri-Universities Libraries
  Donald Baird, SFU's University Librarian, was one of the driving forces behind the formation of the Tri Universities Library (TRIUL) consortium between SFU, the University of British Columbia and the University of Victoria. It informally grew to include all publicly funded libraries in the province. Under the auspices of TRIUL, libraries in B.C. came together to cooperate in the establishment of the British Columbia Union Catalogue (BCUC) and promote other cost saving initiatives for library processing and cataloguing divisions.
  Records include correspondence with partner universities, meeting minutes, reports, statistics, and records of the TRIUL Task Force on Sound Recordings.
  For further records relating to the British Columbia Union Catalogue (BCUC) dating 1977-1985, please see series F-50-8-6, boxes 50-57 and 50-93.
  - TRIUL Task Force on Sound Recordings, 1972 - 1974; F-50-12-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
    Creator's original file classification code: II-A-6.1.
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, 1970 - 1971; F-50-12-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 50-108)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 1, 1971; F-50-12-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 50-109)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 2, 1971; F-50-12-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 50-109)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 3, 1971; F-50-12-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 50-109)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 1, 1972; F-50-12-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 50-109)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 2, 1972; F-50-12-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 50-109)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 3, 1972; F-50-12-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 50-109)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 1, 1973; F-50-12-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 50-109)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 2, 1973; F-50-12-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 50-110)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 3, 1973; F-50-12-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 50-110)
  - TRIUL Directory, 1973 - 1974; F-50-12-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 50-110)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 1, 1974; F-50-12-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 50-110)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 2, 1974; F-50-12-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 50-110)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 3, 1974; F-50-12-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 50-110)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 4, 1974; F-50-12-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 50-110)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 5, 1974; F-50-12-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 50-111)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 1, 1975; F-50-12-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 50-111)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 2, 1975; F-50-12-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 50-111)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 3, 1975; F-50-12-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 50-111)
  - Correspondence, minutes and working papers, vol. 1, 1976; F-50-12-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 50-111)